Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection 1976-1981
AFC 1981/004
Archive of Folk Culture (Library of Congress), collector.; Illinois Arts Council, sponsor.
approximately 14,756 items.
20.75 linear feet.
269 folders in 14 containers.
99 sound tape reels: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono. and stereo.; 7 in.
245 sound cassettes: analog.
3,757 slides: color; 35 mm.
10,182 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm.
202 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 2 1/4 x 2 1/4 in.
2 videocassettes (U-Matic): sound, color; 3/4 in.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
The collection consists of sound recordings, photographs, manuscript materials, videorecordings, publications, ephemera, administrative files, and field notes produced and collected during the 1977 Chicago Ethnic Arts Project field survey from 1976-1981; but primarily during fieldwork conducted by fourteen folklorists directed by the American Folklife Center in 1977. The final project report presented to the Illinois Arts Council summarized the current conditions and folk arts needs in a number of Chicago's ethnic communities. Materials from post-project activities such as workshops in the ethnic communities and a traveling photographic exhibit by Jonas Dovydenas are also included.
Provenance
Accessioned; 1981.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Online Content
The Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection is available on the Library of Congress Web site at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/afconline.afc1981004.
Administrative History
The Chicago Ethnic Arts Project survey was conducted in 1977 by the American Folklife Center at the request of the Illinois Arts Council to assess and document the status of ethnic art traditions in more than twenty ethnic communities in Chicago, and was jointly sponsored by both organizations.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of sound recordings, photographs, manuscript materials, videorecordings, publications, ephemera, administrative files, and field notes produced and collected during the 1977 Chicago Ethnic Arts Project field survey from 1976-1981; but primarily during fieldwork by fourteen folklorists in 1977. The final project report presented to the Illinois Arts Council summarized the current conditions and folk arts needs in these communities. Materials from post-project activities such as workshops in the ethnic communities and a traveling photographic exhibit by Jonas Dovydenas are also included.
Arrangement
The Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection, 1976-1981 is organized in seven series:
Series 1. Administrative, 1977-1978.
Series 2. Collected publications and ephemera, 1938-1979.
Series 3. Documentation: fieldnotes, 1977.
Series 4. Documentation: graphic materials, 1977-1981.
Series 5. Documentation: sound recordings, 1977-1981.
Series 6. Sound Recordings, 1977.
Series 7. Graphic Materials, 1977.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bartis, Peter, 1949-2017; Bradunas, Elena; Brzovich, Mato; Brzovich, Mato--Interviews.; Choi, Chungmoo; Dovydenas, Jonas; Dovydenas, Jonas. Inside our houses, outside our windows.; Epstein, Shifra, 1943-; Fiske-Rusciano, Roberta; Fleischhauer, Carl; George, Philip B., 1946-; González, José Gamaliel, 1933-; Hellenberg, Antony, 1938-2000; Kalčik, Susan J.; Klymasz, Robert Bogdan, 1936-; Klymasz, Shirley; Kubose, Minnie Somi; Kubose, Minnie Somi--Interviews.; Libonati, Roland V. (Roland Victor), 1900-1991; Libonati, Roland V. (Roland Victor), 1900-1991--Interviews.; Lund, Jens, 1946-; Mack, James; March, Richard, 1946-; Mathias, Elizabeth; Metcalfe, Ralph H., 1948-; Moloney, Mick, 1944-2022; Robinson, Beverly J.; Swenson, Greta E.; Trbuhovic-Grasa, Gordana
Organizations
American Folklife Center; American Folklife Center. Report on the Chicago Ethnic Arts Project.; American Indian Center of Chicago.; Archive of Folk Culture (Library of Congress); Chicago Ethnic Arts Project.; Illinois Arts Council
Subjects
African Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Artists--Illinois--Chicago.; Austrian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Bakeries--Illinois--Chicago.; Blues (Music)--1971-1980.; Buddhists--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Catholics--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Chinese Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Community life--Illinois--Chicago.; Costume--Illinois--Chicago.; Croatian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Cuban Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Czech Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Dance, Black--Illinois--Chicago.; Dance--Illinois--Chicago.; Danish Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Dolls--Illinois--Chicago.; Ethnic arts--Illinois--Chicago.; Festivals--Illinois--Chicago.; Field recordings--Illinois--Chicago.; Finnish Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Fishing--Illinois.; Folk dancing--Illinois--Chicago.; Folk music--Illinois--Chicago.; Folklore--Illinois--Chicago.; Fox Indians--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; German Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Greek Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Hispanic Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Indians of North America--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Irish Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Italian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Japanese Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Japanese tea ceremony--Ura Senke school.; Jews--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Korean Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Lithuanian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Macedonian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Murals--Illinois--Chicago.; Music--Illinois--Chicago.; Musical instruments--Illinois--Chicago.; Musicians--Illinois--Chicago.; Needlework--Illinois--Chicago.; Norwegian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Orthodox Eastern Church members--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Parades--Illinois--Chicago.; Pentecostals--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Polish Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Processions, Religious--Illinois--Chicago.; Puerto Ricans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Quilts--Illinois--Chicago.; Serbian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Slovak Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Slovenian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Street art--Illinois--Chicago.; Swedish Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Ukrainian Americans--Illinois--Chicago--Social life and customs.; Weaving--Illinois--Chicago.; Weddings--Illinois--Chicago.; Wood-carving--Illinois--Chicago.
Places
Chicago (Ill.)--Emigration and immigration--Social aspects.; Chicago (Ill.)--Religious life and customs.; Chicago (Ill.)--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre
Ethnography.; Field recordings.; Interviews.; Manuscripts.; Oral histories.; Photographs.; Slides.; Songs.; Sound recordings.; Traveling exhibitions.; Video recordings.; Videocassettes.
Container List
- Series 1: Administrative, 1977-1978
  This section contains materials pertaining to the planning and administration of the Chicago Ethnic Arts Project. Correspondence, schedules, financial records, proposals, and publicity for the project are found here along with information on the fieldworkers and project contacts. Part I of the Report provides a thorough summary and explanation of the purpose and activities of the project; materials in the administration files provide additional details The list of project contacts may be of use to other researchers in the Chicago area.
  - Subseries 1: Planning
    - Pre-project background on Illinois Arts Council (IAC) (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Illinois Arts Council programs, 1978 (FY78) (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Ethnic Arts Panel, list of names (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Letter from Illinois Arts Council to National Endowment for the Arts describing project (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Illinois Arts Council Project Proposal with budget (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Application for financial assistance (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Manuscript on project (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Receipt of grant from Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Tentative travel and media budgets for budget preparation (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Jabbour's first trip to Chicago (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Grant agreement between American Folklife Center and Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Letter from Illinois Arts Council to American Folklife Center (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Planning correspondence with Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Research schedule (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Coordinator's appointment book (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Subseries 2: Fieldworkers
    - Blank fieldworker's contracts (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Peter Bartis (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Chungmoo Choi (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Jonas Dovydenas (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Shifra Epstein (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Roberta Fiske-Hajnal (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Philip George (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Antony Hellenberg (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Susan Kalcik (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Robert Klymasz (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Jens Lund (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Richard March (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Elizabeth Mathias (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Ralph Metcalfe, Jr. (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Mick Moloney (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Beverly Robinson (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Contracts and Resumes, Greta Swenson (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Fieldworkers' addresses and schedules (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Possible fieldworkers (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Media job applicants (Box-folder 2/29)
  - Subseries 3: Actual Project Expenses
    - Coordinator's ledger (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Checking account and bank statements (Box-folder 2/31)
    - GSA vehicles (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Fieldworkers' government driving permits (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Supplies and equipment from American Folklife Center (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Office supplies, apartment bills (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Miscellaneous expenses and statements (Box-folder 2/36)
    - Coordinator's weekly reports (Box-folder 2/37)
    - Media bills (Box-folder 2/38)
    - Post-project expenditures (Box-folder 2/39)
    - Honorariums (Box-folder 2/40)
    - Analysis of proposed budget and actual expenses (Box-folder 3/41)
  - Subseries 4: Publicity and Press Releases
    - Press releases (Box-folder 3/42)
    - Contacts with press and broadcast media (Box-folder 3/43)
    - Ethnic press contacts (Box-folder 3/44)
    - Correspondence with press (Box-folder 3/45)
    - Media coverage (Box-folder 3/46)
      - American (Odessa, TX), May 15, 1977
      - Arts in Illinois pp. 1,7., May/June 1977
      - Belmont Central News (Chicago, IL), June 23, 1977
      - Chicago Daily News, April 18, 1977
      - Chicago Daily News, April 21, 1977
      - Chicago Daily News, April 22, 1977
        Includes 2 versions of the article.
      - Chicago Daily News, June 23, 1977
      - The Chicago Shimpo (Japanese-American), June 17, 1977
      - Courier (Champaign-Urbana, IL), May 31, 1977
      - Chicago Sun-Times, April 19, 1977
      - Hangook Ilbo (in Korean), May 20, 1977
      - Intercommunity Arts, II pp. 1-2., April 1977
      - Lake Shore News, May 10, 1977
      - Library of Congress Information Bulletin, 36, pp. 1-2., April 22, 1977
      - The Lindsborg News-Record (Swedish-American), p 2., May 3, 1977
      - New York Times, August 18, 1977
      - News-Democrat (Belleville, IL), May 31, 1977
      - Viltus: A Folklore Magazine, 36, p 17., September- November, 1977
  - Subseries 5: Correspondence
    - Coordinator's administrative correspondence (Box-folder 3/47)
    - Between American Folklife Center and fieldworkers (Box-folder 3/48)
    - Between fieldworkers and contacts (Box-folder 3/49)
    - Letter with final report to the Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 3/50)
    - General/Miscellaneous (Box-folder 3/51)
  - Subseries 6: Project Contacts
    - Lists of possible contacts (Box-folder 3/52)
    - Address labels for project informants (Box-folder 3/53)
    - Certificate recipients (Box-folder 3/54)
    - Certificate of Appreciation (blank) (Box-folder 3/55)
    - Consulates in Chicago (Box-folder 3/56)
    - Chicago Congressmen (Box-folder 3/57)
  - Subseries 7: Post-Project Materials
    - Notes and documents from presentation by Alan Jabbour to Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 3/58)
- Series 2: Collected publications and ephemera, 1938-1979
  - Subseries 1: General Information about Chicago, resource individuals and institutions
    - Illinois Arts Council (Box-folder 3/59)
      - General information
      - Ethnic festival program
    - Suzanne Craig/Columbia College Folk Artisans survey and directory (Box-folder 3/60)
    - Chicago Historical Society (Box-folder 4/61)
    - Tallman Bank Ethnic Festivals (Box-folder 4/62)
    - South Shore Country Club (Box-folder 4/63)
    - NBC "Small World" program (Box-folder 4/64)
    - Hal Stein, "International Café" radio program (Box-folder 4/65)
    - National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs (Box-folder 4/66)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 4/67)
  - Subseries 2: General Information About Chicago, loose publications
    - Chicago History Vol. V, No. 3 Fall, 1976 (Box-folder 4)
    - Historic City: The Settlement of Chicago Chicago: Dept., of Development and Planning, 1976 (Box-folder 4)
    - International Educational and Cultural Exchange Vol. XII, No. 1 (Box-folder 4)
    - A Survey of Arts and Cultural Activities in Chicago, 1977 Chicago Council on Fine Arts (Box-folder 4)
    - Come for to Sing Vols 1. No.3; 2, No. 1; 2, No. 2; 2, No.3; No. 3, No. 1; 3, No. 2 (Box-folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: General Information about Chicago, Ephemera
    - Bibliographies and notes on books (Box-folder 4/68)
    - Statistics on Chicago (Box-folder 4/69)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box-folder 4/70)
    - Magazine clippings (Box-folder 4/71)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 4/72)
  - Subseries 4: Information on specific Ethnic Groups
    - Afro-American (Box-folder 4/73)
      - Chicago's Black Population: Selected Statistics, 1975
      - Kuumba program and booklet
      - Vita for Haki R. Madhubuti
      - Newspaper and magazine clippings
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
        Contents in envelope.
    - Asian, Chinese (Box-folder 4/74)
      - Chinese American Progress Vol. 26, No. 2, July, 1976
      - Chinese American Progress Vol. 27, No. 1, February, 1977
      - Family Living: A Chinese American Way brochure by the Chinese Community Center, 1974
      - Newspaper clippings
    - Asian, Indian (Box-folder 4/75)
      - Handwritten notes
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Ephemera
    - Asian, Japanese (Box-folder 4/76)
      - Ephemera
    - Asian, Korean (Box-folder 5/77)
      - Friendship Vol. 2, August, 1976
      - Friendship Vol. 3, December, 1976, August, 1976
      - Hangook Hwabo (in Korean), 1976
      - Korean Directory of Chicago The Korean Association of Chicago, 1974
    - Asian, miscellaneous/Pan-Asian (Box-folder 5/78)
      - Ephemera
    - German (Box-folder 5/79)
      - Chicago's German Population: Selected Statistics City of Chicago, November, 1976
      - 39th German American Songfestival, Chicago, 1938
        Bound program book.
      - German-Americans in the Growth of the United States, June 6, 1976
        D.A.N.K. Bicentennial Issue.
      - 200 Jahre USA: Beitrage aus der Bundesrepublik Deutschland. (200 Years USA: Contribution from the Federal Republic of Germany)
      - Brochure for Deutsch Amerikanischer National Kongress (D.A.N.K.) (German-American National Congress)
    - German (Box-folder 5/80)
      - Newspapers (German-American)
    - German (Box-folder 5/81)
      - Hans Bittner, paper cutter
    - German (Box-folder 5/82)
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
      - Phonograph record (Rudy Wacek presents his Zither Album of Most Requested Musical Favorite, Stereo 33 1/3 rpm A Wacek Amplification System Recording, Chicago, Ill. Synchro-Tone, ST 108. Electric zither soloist.)
      - Phonograph record (Chicago Zither Club, 60th Anniversary Album 1913-1973.), 33 1/3 rpm. Mono record by Syochro-Tone, ST 110.
    - Greek (Box-folder 5/83)
      - Bibliography of Greek-Americans, by Peter Bartis
      - Outlines of courses on Greek-Americans
      - The Greek Star: The Voice of Chicago's Hellenic Community. Vol. 76, No. 3803, March 29, 1979
      - F.K. Litsas, Rousalia: The Ritual Worship of the Dead, in World Anthropology, ed. by Sol Tax. The Hague: Mouton Publishers, 1975
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Miscellaneous Ephemera
      - Phonograph record John Georganas Sings. Stereo 33 1/3 rpm. Produced by John Georganas Record Co. Jacket notes and title in Greek
      - Phonograph record Stereo 45 rpm. By John Hemonas, composer and singer. Barselona Records. Side A -"America, America;" Side B, "Rantevou Stosintagma."
    - Irish (Box-folder 5/84)
      - Chicago's Irish Population: Selected Statistics. City of Chicago, November, 1976
      - Shanachie Newsletter No. 3, December, 1976
      - Friedman, Emily, Irish Music in Chicago, Come for to Sing, Vol. 3, pp. 16-18, winter 1977
      - Selected bibiography from Funchion, Michael F. Chicago's Irish Nationalists 1881-1890. New York: Arno, 1976
      - Miscellaneous handwritten notes
      - Clippings
    - Italian (Box-folder 5/85)
      - Chicago's Italian Population: Selected Statistics. City of Chicago, 1976
      - McBride, Paul W. The Italians in America: An Interdisciplinary Bibliography. American Italian Historical Association, 1975
      - Santucci, Elio. Poesie e Canzoni da Chicago. Campobasso: Edizioni "Il Pungolo Verde,", 1974
      - Bibliography from Schiavo, Giovanni Ermenegildo. The Italians in Chicago: A Study, in Americanization. NY: Arno, reprint of 1928 original, 1975
    - Italian (Box-folder 5/86)
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Jewish (Box-folder 6/87)
      - Grace, KTAV Publishing House, Inc., 1964
      - Silver, Manuel, ed. Guide to Jewish Chicago. Chicago: American Jewish Congress, 1976
      - Labor Zionist Alliance of Chicago Third Seder, program book, 1970
      - Labor Zionist Alliance of Chicago Third Seder, program book, 1976
      - Labor Zionist Organization of Chicago Third Seder, program book, 1977
      - Chicago chapter of Hadassah, program book
    - Jewish (Box-folder 6/88)
      - Ephemera from the Yiddish Theatre Association
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Latino (Spanish-speaking, Filipino) (Box-folder 6/89)
      - Chicago's Spanish-Speaking Population: Selected Statistics. City of Chicago, 1973
      - The Fifth Annual Puerto Rican Parade, program book, June 13, 1970
      - Puerto Rican Congress of Mutual Aid Inc. Sixteenth Anniversary, Awards and Banquet
      - First Hispanic Classical Super-Concert of Chicago, program book, June 18, 1977
      - Pino, Frank. Mexican Americans: A Research Bibliography. Michigan State University, 1974
        Xerox copy.
      - Bravo, Enfrique R., ed. Bibliografie Puertorriquena Selecta y Anotada. NY: The Urban Center of Columbia Archive, 1972
        Includes xerox of table of contents.
      - Vivo, Paquita, ed. The Puerto Ricans: An Annotated Bibliography. NY: R.R. Bowker Co.,, 1973
    - Latino (Box-folder 6/90)
      - Newspaper clippings
    - Latino (Box-folder 6/91)
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Latino, Filipino only (Box-folder 6/92)
      - The Philippines Herald, June 8, 1977
      - Filipino Reporter, June 10-16, 1977
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Lithuanian (Box-folder 6/93)
      - Newspapers
    - Lithuanian (Box-folder 6/94)
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Native American (Box-folder 6/95)
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Polish (Box-folder 6/96)
      - Chicago's Polish Population: Selected Statistics. City of Chicago, 1976
      - Notes on Polish resource individuals
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
      - Phonograph record (Bialo - Czerwoni, White and Red [name of group], Stereo 33 1/3 rpm.)
    - Polish, Alvin Sajewski, Polish music store (Box-folder 6/97)
      - Program for 80th anniversary dinner
      - Invitation to testimonial dinner
      - Drafts for Greta Swenson's speech at the dinner
      - Talk by Rev. Madaj of Polish Museum of America
      - Chicago Daily News, May 16, 1977
      - Miscellaneous notes
    - Russian (Box-folder 6/98)
      - Ephemera from Holy Trinity Russian Orthodox Cathedral
      - Ephemera from St. Vladimir's Seminary
    - Scandinavian (Box-folder 7/99)
      - Danish American Athletic Club, program books for 50th and 54th anniversary exhibitions
      - Finland: Travel Facts. Helsinki: The Finnish Tourist Board, 1977
      - Focus on Finland. Helsinki: Ministry for Foreign Affairs, 1976
      - Herva, Marjatta. Let's Have a Sauna. Helsinki: Sauna-Seura, 1973
      - Kontakt (Newsletter from the Norwegian Lutheran Memorial Church) No. 6, No. 1, 1977
      - Madsen, N.B. ed. Danish American Athletic Club. Chicago: Danish American Athletic Club, 1943
      - The Society for the Danish Old People's Home, 84th Annual Report. Chicago:, May, 1975
      - Svendka Amerikanaren Tribunen (The Swedish American Newspaper) (Chicago), 1977
      - The Vasa Star, Vol. 70, No. 5, May, 1977
    - Scandinavian (Box-folder 7/100)
      - Music and program book from Chicago Norwegian National League 17th of May celebration music scores
      - Music scores
    - Scandinavian (Box-folder 7/101)
      - Lists and notes of resource individuals
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - South Slavic, Czech, and Slovak (Box-folder 7/102)
      - Pan-Yugoslavian ephemera
    - South Slavic, Czech, and Slovak, Serbian (Box-folder 7/103)
      - Newspaper clippings
      - Xeroxes of back jacket covers of the Popovich Brothers' recordings
      - List of Serbo-Croatian phonograph records
    - South Slavic, Czech, and Slovak, Slovenian (Box-folder 7/104)
      - Zarja the Dawn (Official publication of Slovenian Women's Union), 8 issues
    - South Slavic, Czech, and Slovak, Czechoslovakian (Box-folder 7/105)
      - The Czechoslovakian Society of America Journal, May, 1977
      - List of Czech and Slovak phonograph records
      - Miscellaneous ephemera
    - Southern Whites (Box-folder 7/106)
      - The Great American Coffeehouse, poster and program
      - The Old Country Church, program and letter
      - Northside United Pentecostal Church, tracts
    - Ukrainian (Box-folder 7/107)
      - Samchyshyn, Miroslav, ed. The Ukrainians: Facts about Ukraine and the Ukrainian People. Chicago: The Ukrainian Congress Committee in America, 1977
      - Publications in Ukrainian
    - Ukrainian (Box-folder 7/108)